[
  {
    "question": "What do you call an Aussie with a bottle of Champagne?",
    "answer": "A waiter."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Ricky Ponting put in his hands to make sure the next ball is almost certainly going to be a wicket?",
    "answer": "A bat."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call a world-class Australian cricketer?",
    "answer": "Retired."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call an Australian who can hold a catch?",
    "answer": "A fisherman."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why can no-one drink wine in Australia at the moment?",
    "answer": "They haven't got any openers ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the difference between Cinderella and the Aussies?",
    "answer": "Cinderella knew when to leave the ball."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does an Australian batsman who is playing in The Ashes have in common with Michael Jackson?",
    "answer": "They both wore gloves for no apparent reason."
  },
  {
    "question": "Who spends the most time on the crease of anyone on the Australian cricket team?",
    "answer": "The person who irons their cricket whites."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call an Aussie holding a six inch urn above his head?",
    "answer": "The England bowling coach."
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the height of optimism?",
    "answer": "An Aussie batsman putting on sunscreen."
  }
]